## LESLIE DOMINIQUE



#### CONTACT

lad191@miami.edu

973-943-7766

Sandy Springs, GA 30328

### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Expected in 05/2022

Bachelor of Arts - Broadcast Journalism

University Of Miami Coral Gables, FL

Minor in International Relations Minor in Psychology

# WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

- Reel: https://youtu.be /NA72wXldujY
- IG: @luvlyleslie
- Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/leslie-anne-dominique-65bb141bb

#### SKILLS

- Broadcast Writing
- Reporting

#### SUMMARY

Leslie Anne Dominique, a junior at the University of Miami, majors in Broadcast Journalism with minors in International Relations and Psychology. Leslie Anne has a strong background in reporting, editing, and producing for various University of Miami television shows, as well as Instagram Television Productions and she also serves as the Public Relations chair of a campus organization. Her written work has been published in print and digital media. Leslie Anne's interests currently lie within Broadcast Journalism and Media Relations.

#### MEDIA EXPERIENCE

#### Anchor

**UMTV: The Pulse** | Coral Gables, FL

09/2020 - Current Report, write and edit celebrity entertainment news in study and on IGTV. Also conduct an advice segment.

#### Anchor

UMTV: NewsBreak | Coral Gables, FL

01/2021 - Current Responsible for writing, and reporting news on local, national and international levels.

#### **Associate Producer**

**UMTV: The Culture** | Coral Gables, FL

01/2021 - Current Responsible for editing packages, and in studio production including; camera work, teleprompter managing, etc.

#### **Segment Producer**

UMTV: The Culture Uncensored | Coral Gables, FL

08/2020 - Current Responsible for organizing and editing videos, conducting interviews for The Culture Uncensored on IGTV.

#### **Published Writer**

University of Miami's Distraction Magazine | Coral Gables, FL

07/2020 - Current Published in both print and digital formats of Distraction Magazine.

#### **Assistant Digital Editor**

- Microsoft Suite
- Google Workspace
- Fact-checking
- Story pitching
- Research skills
- Phone Etiquette
- Conducting interviews
- Editing
- Producing
- Improvisation
- ENPS
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Premiere
- Adobe InDesign
- Spanish
- Guitar-playing
- HTML Coding
- CSS Coding
- JAVA

#### University of Miami's Distraction Magazine | Coral Gables, FL

06/2020 - Current Responsible for editing and writing online articles.

#### Anchor

UMTV: The Culture | Coral Gables, FL

01/2020 - 12/2020 News anchor and host for a round table talk about major topics in the Black community.

#### Shadow

WSB-TV | Atlanta, GA

06/2019 - 08/2019 Shadowed News Anchor, Wendy Corona, observed her on set and on location.

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

- Waitress, University of Miami Rathskeller, Coral Gables, FL, 2018 2020
- Waitress, Nancy's Pizzeria, Dunwoody, GA, 2018 present
- Hostess, Monty's Raw Bar & Grill, Coconut Grove, FL, 2021 present

#### **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- Miss Congeniality at Planet Kreyol Pageant 2019
- University of Miami Deans List

#### **ACTIVITIES AND HONORS**

- Member, Distraction Magazine's Diversity Council (2020-present)
- Orientation Fellow, University of Miami (2020 -present)
- Public Relations Chair, **Planet Kreyol: Haitian Student Org** (2020- present)
- Creative Team Member, Caribbean Student Association, (2019 2020)